The End Move along, Lene.
Coming, Miss Claire.
Ray, are you almost done?
What in the world is that
Commoner doing? Honestly.
We don't have all day,
Ray Taylor. Hurry up! Kay!
Ray Taylor is what I've
been called since I
was reincarnated in my
favorite dating sim.
Hmm.
Telling the villainess of the game I was
in love with her kinda complicated things.
But now I'm remade and loving every
minute I get to spend by your side.
What you made from that?
This is a real experience!
I know you're the best.
Yeah, it's annoying.
I know, I know you're the best!
I love
you're
the best.
If you don't like it,
if you don't like it,
it's not going to start with the feeling.
So let your heart be right now.
The love of love is only one thing.
From the heart of the heart.
Let your heart be right now.
Rei-chan-han, one more time!
I don't want to die until I die!
It's interesting, I love you!
Whoa, whoa.
Not bad.
You've got some skills.
Oh, no. Not at all.
Don't play humble.
Until now, you's been the only
one who could challenge me.
So you resign, right?
How dare you!
Mind your tongue when
speaking to Prince Rod!
It's fine, Claire.
To answer your question,
I'm not resigning.
Checkmate.
You're good, but not better.
Congratulations you saw
that coming didn't you
halfway through you
started playing to counter.
You noticed that's
impressive i'm surprised as
well i wasn't aware that
you had a knack for.
The game neither was i are all
commoners chess masters like you who
knows this is actually The first time
i've ever tried it what really you
were that good on your first go i
know the rules On how to play it i've
just never played on an actual chess
set that doesn't make any sense.
I promise i'm not lying
in revolution there's
an ai chess game you can
play it allows you to
Challenge any of the
characters let me tell you
i played the heck out of
it first the magic exams
And now this you're full
of surprises aren't you
ray taylor well thanks
for the match i had a lot
Of fun should we be on
our way now miss claire
um we should all right
let's play again sometime
And when we do no need to hold back.
Oh crap he knows i was going easy on him.
I'm not trying to make
it weird i just really
really need to lower his affection level.
Oh, commoner?
Prince Yu, would you care for some tea?
Would you like to try any of these sweets?
They're new.
Thank you.
Let's see how you pull out of this.
Out of all the moves you could have made.
Okay.
Move the queen to F4.
That should stare the whole
game in your direction!
Try it.
Thank you for your unsolicited advice.
However, I'll ask that you not
distract me during a match!
Especially to suggest a
move I was about to make.
My apologies.
I just hate to see Rey
being so unfair to you?
You didn't notice?
She is deliberately putting you on the
offensive to walk you into her trap.
Right I see you're hoping to win with
cowardly tactics guilty but every time.
We play you're on the attack so I thought
I'd change it up I'm sorry easy glare.
What do you say we give it a rest for
now may I tempt you with some poker now?
Then deed you'll be our dealer it's an
honor sir thanks for coming Misha and on.
Short notice of course Misha's a proper
busy lady you know you should be honored.
she showed up for you.
There's no need to be rude, Ray.
Please accept my apologies, Prince Hugh.
I'll be sure to give her a talking to.
Oh, no, I don't mind.
You know, you can feel free to adopt
a more informal approach with me, too.
As students, we are all on the same level.
Hey, Miss Claire, did you see what I saw?
They're pretty cute together, aren't they?
I think I may have caught
a whiff of love in the air.
Why is every single idea that pops
into your mind so dreadfully vulgar?
Aren't they adorable?
They were really good friends as children.
They remained quite close until
Misha's family fell on hard times.
We're not supposed to know, but Misha's
got a pretty hardcore crush on him.
Shh.
You are allowed to swap
out cards up to two times.
There are no chips.
The only object of the game is to
have the strongest hand showing.
Hmm.
Not bad at all.
One draw away from a street.
I'd like to swap out one card.
I'll take two. Huh?
Now that is a poker face!
Misha has got it down to an art!
Tell me, Ray.
Whilst playing chess with Rod earlier,
were you holding back so he could win?
Ray, is that true?
You threw the game for the
prince's benefit? No way!
I swear that guy gives me too much credit!
My, my.
You truly are quite a fascinating girl.
But please, don't hold back in this game.
I only have one card I'd
care to swap, please.
If she gets any cuter, I might explode!
She's clearly got a great hand.
Get him, girl.
I'll stick with the cards I have.
All right, we're on to the second round.
Swap or stay?
He's not even swapping out a single card?
Interesting.
He must have a really good hand.
If so, then a straight
won't be enough to beat him.
I'm gonna need to swap them all.
It's kind of a risky move so early on.
But I have to win.
I can't wait to see Miss
Claire's frustrated face.
I think we're ready to show hands.
Ray first.
It's called trash!
Biggie food!
Not your lucky day, is it?
Misha?
Three of a kind
And you, Claire?
The look on your face says you've
also got an impressive hand.
A foe house, in fact!
I'm living for that laugh!
Well then, looks like it's my turn.
I don't have much.
Just four of a kind.
That's incredible, Prince Yu.
Whoa, wasn't that an ace of hearts?
I had one of those in my original hand.
I get it now.
The dealer is Prince Yu's attendant.
This game was totes rigged.
I should have guessed.
Ray, is there something
you'd like to share?
No, nothing.
I'm on to you, Prince Charlatan!
I must admit that's not
the response I expected.
A fascinating girl indeed.
What is this about?
Did you do something underhanded again?
No, I was good, I swear!
Anyway, shouldn't we get going now?
If this keeps up, we're gonna
lose Misha to the dark side.
I know that sound miss
claire i hope there's a
reason for your bellowing
i need you to come with
me ray slow down what
are you doing don't drag
me behind you like a dog
shh behold my gift to you
Prince Thane!
All alone playing a harp?
Oh, lovely.
It's not as random as it seems.
This is one of his game events.
Turns out that broody Prince
Thane has mad harp skills.
The protagonist has the option
to compliment him on it, but...
That was the most beautiful
sound I've ever heard!
As soon as you started
playing, I felt less alone.
You have a gift for
harpsmanship. Ugh! Why?
She couldn't have made a
bigger mistake if she tried!
He wasn't done!
If you want to raise his affection level,
you gotta listen to the whole
thing before approaching him!
Do not engage him while he's in the zone!
He hates that!
Oh, are you finished playing already?
It is nothing worth subjecting others to.
This is a frivolous pastime.
It has nothing to do
with being a good king.
Here's an idea.
Why don't we play a game that will
test your suitability to become king?
Now, wait a minute. Explain.
I'm curious as well.
What sort of game could test something
so complex? Perhaps chess? Oh, no.
This one's much more innovative. Trust me.
It is called the king game.
What is the king game?
We all draw lots with numbers on them,
and if you draw the number one,
that means you're the king.
Guess what the king does.
Numbers X and Y have to do Z.
He or she gets to give
orders to everyone else.
That's it.
Any questions?
Should we expect to know which one of
us will be the best ruler after playing?
For sure.
Are you ready to play?
And go!
Who's the king now? My
word. What was that?
Oh, it's a standard part of the game.
We all have to say it
when it's time to reveal
the results of the drawing
and crown the king.
All of us at once?
All of us at once. No exceptions?
No exceptions!
I see.
Okay, are we ready to
try this for realsies?
Who's the king? Now!
It is I. That's right!
You're the king, Prince Thane.
So, give your orders.
Alright then.
Numbers two and three, I
order you to hold hands.
Number two!
And I have been cursed
with a number three.
It's an order!
Hey, stop!
He said hold my hand!
There was no mention of stroking!
But I don't have a choice!
The king ordered me to do it, Miss Claire!
We do what we must for, hand and control!
I didn't order you to go that far.
I've had enough!
Let's move on to the next round!
Who's the king now?
Oh, it's me this time.
Very well, Lene.
Let's get on with it.
Hmm, okay, what to do?
Let's see.
Oh, number four must pat number
three lovingly on the head.
That is me, four.
Um, and I'm number three.
I think that crosses the line.
I don't believe one should touch
a lady's hair without consent.
Oh, you most certainly have
my consent, Prince Thane.
I don't mind.
Well then, if I may...
Oh, wow.
Yay, end to the third round!
Who's the king now?
Who?
Destiny takes a hand!
Now, what shall be my first degree?
What sort of ridiculous
order is she going to give?
One, two, three.
Solanae's number three.
Rey, what on earth are you thinking?
Wait, you wanna cheat? Yep.
If one of us becomes king,
all the other one has to do is signal
what her number is by blinking, Hmm,
which will let us know what Ms.
Claire and Prince Dane's numbers are, too.
And then, boom, we give them a spicy
order that makes the magic happen.
Oh, I guess we could, but...
She loves Ms.
Claire, so why is she doing this?
Okay, I've decided.
My order is that number two
and number four must kiss. Ah!
You heard me.
Numbers two and four must kiss.
Now hold on a moment, commoner.
I am sure you know that
order is - Absolute.
Yeah, that tends to be the
case with the king's orders.
I'm not sure what you're waiting for.
I see now.
I certainly don't.
Ray Taylor, you were lying.
This game has nothing to
do with being a good king.
Were you mocking me?
Can't get anything past
you, can we? Pardon?
You correctly deduced
that this game has nothing
to do with whether you'll
be a great king someday.
As it happens, the true objective was to
see how long it took you to figure it out.
Well done.
You're saying it was a test.
And for that, I humbly
ask for your forgiveness.
On the bright side,
you refused to comply with
an unreasonable order,
and you successfully
identified my true intentions.
I'd say you have what it takes.
Only a true king could
sort through all that.
I'm leaving.
Prince Zane, wait!
This won't happen again.
Mark my words.
Ray, was this whole thing really a test?
Nope, I lied. What?
You deceptive snake!
What's wrong with you?
Oh, so much.
But hey, at least I managed to
score you some sweet headpacks!
Ray, tell me, am I correct in assuming
that you're what they call gay?
Miss Misha,
don't you think that's an awfully
personal question to ask in this setting?
It's an awfully personal question
for any setting if you ask me!
It doesn't bother me to
talk about it, but...
Why do you want to know?
Well, you are my best
friend, so I'm curious.
Hmm, I mean, I guess?
If it means I like girls, then yeah.
I've never been in love with a guy before.
Hey, you don't look so
good, what's the matter?
I'm sensing that I am in danger!
That's what!
That's not fair.
I understand you might be leery of
Rei, given how she often behaves.
But Miss Claire, to react that
way just because she's gay?
It says more about your ignorance
than it does her character.
I'll explain.
Let's say, as an example,
that you are straight.
I am straight, Misha!
And you're madly in love with
Prince Thane, aren't you?
You're the one who mad-loved me!
Ray, the jokes aren't helpful.
So, tell me, Miss Claire.
How would you feel if a man came up to
you and said, Don't molest me? What?
I would never conduct myself
in a lecherous manner!
Of course you wouldn't.
And yet, you basically
accused Ray of the same thing.
You said you were in danger.
Yeah, you're so right, Misha.
It doesn't work like that.
No one lusts after everyone who
fits their gender preference.
It doesn't matter if
you're gay or straight.
Attraction is based on the individual.
Yes, that's true.
I see your point.
You're saying you fall in love with
the person and not their gender, right?
And currently, the one you're in
love with just happens to be a woman.
Is that the case?
No, I mean, not exactly.
I wouldn't say gender
doesn't matter at all.
Oh, then it does?
Yeah.
I get the logic behind
saying gender doesn't
matter when you deeply
connect with someone.
Like, love is love.
But I can say for sure that I'll never
have those kinds of feelings for a man.
I guess all of this is more
complicated than people think.
Some people never have
the chance to learn.
They can't help that.
And I know Miss Clara
doesn't feel the same way.
I'm just happy to bask in her presence.
But if you ever change your mind and
you want to make out, just let me know.
I never will!
And it's because you
continue to say those things
that I feel like I have to
remain forever on my guard!
For the record, I agree with every
part of that last bit. But why?
I really don't ever expect anyone
to reciprocate my feelings.
And besides...
Go on. What is it?
Nothing, never mind.
I'm not the only one who's
been unlucky in love.
I have to remember that.
Finish your thought.
Were you about to say you've
given up on Miss Claire?
Am I not supposed to respond
to this conversation?
Do they realize I'm mere inches away?
Actually, I'm a little
confused about that, too.
It's just, from the
way you've been acting,
I assumed you were in
love with Miss Claire.
But then you suggested we cheat in that
game to help her get close to Prince Thane.
I'm still here!
And I believe I heard
something I cannot overlook!
I wonder what that could be!
I don't think I said anything!
Well, I don't know.
I have never thought of it in that way
before, that I would be giving up on her.
I've always known she's straight,
so it's not as though I expected us
to ride off into the sunset together.
Miss Claire has chosen someone she
loves, and I want to support her in that.
And besides, I'm honestly
happy just being around her.
But most importantly, it was never
about being physical with her.
That isn't my end goal.
All I want is to make her happy.
Genuinely happy.
So yeah,
if you're questioning whether I can give
up on something that brings me so much joy,
I'm afraid the answer is no.
I see.
Anyway, don't worry about me, Miss Claire.
You just keep treating me
the way you always have.
Um, all right.
Honestly, I am content with our
relationship exactly as it is.
Beef bowls, extra large servings today.
Oh, heck yeah!
Talking about all those super complex
subjects made me anxious and hungry.
I'm gonna go get a beef bowl!
Would you get one for me?
I'd like one, too.
Beef bowls have been acquired!
I brought you one, too,
just in case you're hungry.
No, thank you.
Everything's definitely as it was before.
See nothing's changed at all.
The world of happiness
and pain.
I'm used to it.
Though almost no one I've loved
has ever returned my feelings.
As long as I don't tell them how
I feel they'll remain in my life.
But the moment I fall in
love I lose them completely.
Look it's that commoner.
Oh right.
The one who's been pursuing Miss Claire.
Even though they're both girls.
Maybe it's my fault.
Maybe it's my behavior that's
creating their prejudice.
Why do the princes even talk to her.
I suppose strange people
make for good entertainment.
That must be it.
It's not like anyone could ever
be attracted to a freak like her.
I don't mind.
As long as I keep making jokes about
the rejection, I can hold it together.
Oh, I can be awfully clumsy sometimes.
Miss Claire, are you okay?
I'm sorry, I wasn't paying attention
and my hand must have slipped.
You're alright though, aren't you?
You did that on purpose.
I said you're alright, aren't you?
Yes, ma 'am.
Commoner!
Yes?
You've dawdled over your meal long enough.
If you've finished eating, I
have several things to get done.
I never imagined that Miss
Claire would stand up for Ray.
Yes, well, I don't know if I'd
call that standing up for her.
She may not have meant to,
but Miss Claire did something
wrong, and she realizes that.
It left her feeling unsettled.
Fortunately,
though, two girls happen to
come along spouting insults,
providing the perfect target on which to
release all of that self-directed anger.
Miss Claire is still very much a child.
Avoid the pickled ginger.
It is way too sour to eat.
Well, it's supposed to be sour.
That's the appeal.
Um, Miss Claire?
What is it?
Do you have some sort of problem?
Well, not really, no.
Um...
I'm just curious.
I mean, I want to know
if you still hate me.
You do, right?
Of course I still hate you!
Thank you!
And I still love you!
Thank you.
I love you.
I'm excited!
I'm so happy, I'm so happy!
I'm so happy, and you're so happy!
I'm happy, and I don't want
to know what I'm doing!
I'm so happy, and that's
why I'm so happy! Oh wow!
This world's living in a
world that's going forward!
Don't you ask me!
I want to learn my life!
I'd like to play with you!
I'm off to go practice my
magic skills for next week.
Oh, are you suggesting that even
a dual caster needs to prepare?
Even with protag specs, I still
can't afford to slack off.
Love, effort, victory.
So on the note, give me your love.
I don't know what you're talking about.